[explosions]
[man screams]
[tense action music playing]
Pirates! They're too strong!
Come on!
[woman grunts]
[man panting]
Hurry!
[woman screams]
[man] Hurry! Hurry!
[grunts]
[woman 2] You lot are pathetic.
[man 2] You said it.
I knew the East Blue was
supposed to be weak, but sheesh.
-[woman grunts] -[laughs]
[grunts]
[scoffs] Now I've got
Marine all over my heels.
[sighs]
This is boring.
What are we doing in
this backwater base anyway?
[woman 3] It's called due
diligence, Miss Valentine.
Hmm.
[action music swells]
Guard the doors!
Commander Ripper!
Commander Ripper, the outer
perimeter's been breached.
Pirates have entered the base.
Remember your oaths.
To uphold justice, we will
absolutely hold this line.
[mystical tinkling]
[music stops]
[footsteps approaching]
Hmm.
That's quite a lot of arms you have.
[inhales sharply]
Doce Fleur.
[mystical tinkling]
[grunts]
[Marine screams]
[grunting]
Charge!
[Marines yell]
[mysterious action music playing]
[Marines screaming]
[grunts]
[muffled screaming]
[gun cocks]
Aah!
[gasping]
Where do you keep your dead?
Looks like we need a new Mr. 7.
Or at least a
Mr. Three-and-a-half.
[Miss Valentine laughs]
-How disappointing. -Yeah, which part?
One of our agents biting the dust?
Or the East Blue punk that did it
turning down an
invitation to Baroque Works?
-Both. -Mr. Zero's not gonna be happy.
No. I can't imagine he will be.
Good thing he's got us.
This is the handiwork of
Roronoa Zoro, is it not?
Bye-bye, darling. [kisses]
We need to find him.
He… he left.
His captain attacked
the base and freed him.
Then they escaped and
made for the Grand Line.
You telling us the pirate
hunter is a pirate himself?
Awkward.
Who is this captain?
Monkey D. Luffy.
Interesting.
Where is it?
Whoa, rude!
I was using that pepper.
Usopp, you have your tools. I have mine.
You don't see me grabbing
any of your rubber bands
and tossing them into a soufflé.
Yeah, because that would
make a terrible soufflé.
But these new pepper bombs?
The latest and greatest in
Captain Usopp's mighty arsenal.
I hope those bombs of yours are edible
'cause I'm running low on supplies.
Between the way Luffy eats
and whatever it is you do…
Innovative genius?
A miracle I can keep
scrounging meals together.
The kitchen's not the
only thing that's hurting.
We're also low on ship
maintenance supplies,
first-aid supplies.
Sounds expensive.
But necessary.
[both] Better talk to Nami.
[Sanji] Nami, love, for lunch today,
we have a sautéed black pepper octopus.
Thank you, Sanji.
You have octopus. I had egg sandwich.
[Nami] Mmm.
You have outdone
yourself, as always, Sanji.
I aim to please.
Although, for black pepper octopus,
I don't taste very much pepper.
So I think I have found our
best route into the Grand Line.
We're not too far off, but
there's dangerous traversal ahead.
Looks like this waterway here
cuts right through the Red Line.
I'm not the navigator,
but doesn't this open ocean
seem like a way safer option
than sailing through a mountain?
It connects right to the Grand Line.
Well, good thing you are not the navigator,
or we would all be screwed.
This is the Calm Belt.
I'm guessing it's not named
that for its easy travel.
No. It is named for its
still water and lack of wind.
You enter the Calm Belt, and
your sails instantly hang limp.
No way to move.
Becalmed and dead in the water.
- Also a breeding ground for sea kings.
- Oh, yeah. Let's not go there.
I killed a bunch of them once.
- We got a lot of bad blood, so it's like…
- Why don't we go to Loguetown?
That sounds like a perfectly
safe, non-dangerous place to visit.
I like this.
Loguetown is the largest Marine
hub in all of the East Blue.
Let's not go there. I changed by mind.
Let's go straight for the Grand Line.
No, there's gotta be some
safer islands around here.
It doesn't seem like it.
We're low on food and
pretty much everything.
This could be our last chance
to stock up before the Grand Line.
It is dangerous to enter
the Grand Line underprepared,
and we're not far away. Maybe we could...
[Sanji] You're free for
the first time in your life.
Haven't you earned the right to
buy yourself a little something nice?
No. No.
Don't you fall for it.
I could do with a little shopping.
-Yeah! -What?! What?!
Curse you, Sanji! Curse you!
And your charm and your
chiseled jawline, your ocean eyes.
We need someone who can talk
some sense into the… Zoro! Zoro!
Buddy, back me up here.
Sanji and Nami wanna go to an
island full of Marines to shop,
which I think is stupid considering
me and Luffy are on a wanted poster now.
Tell 'em you agree with me.
[Zoro] Hmm.
-Shopping? -Yeah. Can you believe it?
-Good idea. -What?!
I need two more swords.
I've been feeling off.
Since the sword-shattering
arse-kicking Mihawk gave you?
- Shut up! You weren't even there.
- [Sanji] I saw what I needed to.
Sorry, Usopp. That's
another vote for Loguetown.
- This isn't over yet. Where's Luffy?
- Where do you think?
[Zoro] Hey, Luffy! Crew meeting.
[adventurous music playing]
Coming!
Okay. What's up?
Luffy! Uh…
I've always respected
your position as captain.
Now's time for you to put your
foot down with these hooligans,
otherwise we're gonna get killed.
-What do you mean? -We need to make a stop.
But we're going to the Grand
Line so I can find the One Piece...
And become King of the Pirates.
And we wanna get there, too, Luffy,
but we need to stop in Loguetown
to get some things first.
-What's in Loguetown? -Death!
I don't want that.
I need new swords.
Good. That could help with the death.
And we need more food
for the journey ahead.
Even better.
[Nami] And
it's also the place where
Gold Roger was executed.
The place where the King of
the Pirates was born and died.
Where the legend of the One Piece was born.
You want to see it, don't you?
[chuckles]
You know I do!
And you thought we were
gonna skip Loguetown.
[adventurous music continues]
All right, Straw Hats, set course to…
Wait, which way? Okay.
Set course to Loguetown!
[uplifting music playing]
[theme music playing]
[crowd clamoring]
[door opens]
[door creaks]
Vice Admiral.
[keys jangle]
[Garp] I'm sorry about the accommodations.
Not really fit for the
Pirate King, are they?
It wasn't me that came up with
that moniker now, though, was it?
So, Monkey D. Garp.
The hero of God Valley.
The man who captured Gold Roger.
Quite the feathers in your cap.
When's the next parade?
[Garp] Later today.
And there is a special
seat saved just for you.
[Gold Roger chuckles]
Of all the battles that
we've had over the years, Garp,
it's the verbal sparring that
I've always enjoyed the most.
Not me.
It's the beating the piss out
of you up and down the Grand Line,
that was my favorite.
[both chuckling]
[both laughing]
[coughing]
Yeah.
[sighs]
You learn a lot about what
a man's made of in combat.
The clashing of steel.
The feel of his blood
dripping from your knuckles.
Tells you what's in his heart.
In his soul.
We've come to blows many times.
I know you, Garp.
I trust you.
As if you were one of my own crew.
Which is why I have one final favor to ask.
I have a son.
I need you to find him,
care for him, keep him safe.
[suspenseful music playing]
Why are you asking this of me?
Because no son
should have to suffer
for the sins of his father.
[Garp] And what makes
you think I'll do this?
Because you're a good man.
[Garp] A good man who's about
to lead you to the gallows.
True.
But I trust you won't
do the same to my son.
Night may be falling
on my time, but his dawn,
it's only just beginning.
You've cursed me for the last time.
[sighs]
[keys jangle]
[lock rattles]
[door creaks]
[Gold Roger] It isn't over, Garp.
Piracy isn't over.
Yes, it is.
[suspenseful music swells]
Woo-hoo!
[upbeat, adventurous music playing]
[Luffy] Yeah!
[indistinct chatter]
[Luffy] Wow, we're really here.
[Sanji] So many people.
Look at this place!
[horn honks]
Loguetown.
The town of the beginning and the end.
[Luffy] This is where it all started.
The hunt for the One Piece.
History happened here!
[Sanji] It looks like they're
having some kind of festival.
For Gold Roger's execution.
A festival? Not so good for laying low.
Then we'll just have to be smart.
No attracting unnecessary attention.
I want to see the execution platform.
Of course you do.
Sanji, what if you took Luffy
with you for some food shopping?
-Mmm? -Food first, then execution platform.
Right! Food will keep him out of trouble.
I am headed to the fashion district.
Zoro, you need new swords, right?
I need money too.
Okay, what do you want me to do about that?
The cook got money.
I'm buying food for all of us.
- Me having more swords is for all of us.
- Mm-hmm.
God, what I wouldn't give
for another girl on the crew.
You take this, you pay me back.
With 300% interest.
The…
-What if I need more? -You haggle.
There's a price that they want
and a price that they will take.
Haggle.
Fine.
[Nami] Let's get our stuff
and get back to the ship.
I'm gonna stay with Nami.
Young woman in the big city.
You gotta keep her safe.
My hero.
[Luffy] Ah.
All right, we meet back
here when we are done,
and remember, this is a large
Marine town, so keep a low…
- [Luffy] Hello, Loguetown!
- [Sanji] Luffy, wait up.
…profile.
[suspenseful music playing]
What are you standing around for?
- Fish my haul out, will ya?
- [man] Yes, Captain Smoker.
Sir, you… you caught
Koze of the Yes Pirates.
His partner wasn't fortunate enough
to catch a ride back to Loguetown.
[Koze breathing shakily]
Ah.
No pirate escapes me.
- Where the hell's Tashigi?
- Sir, I haven't seen her today.
That girl…
This time of year brings all the wannabe
pirates to Loguetown. We have to be ready.
Throw this scum in the brig.
I'm going on patrol.
[waiter] Here you go, ladies.
Feels good finally buying
something for myself for once.
Yeah. You sure have bought a lot.
Ignoring that comment
for your own well-being.
I should get something to
conceal my true identity.
Oh yeah. These'll do the trick.
[indistinct chatter]
[curious music playing]
[Usopp] Cool book.
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Yeah, it's, um…
It's an Atlas of the East Blue.
I had one just like it when I was a kid.
For a time, anyway.
-You should get it. -What? No.
No, I'm supposed to be drawing my
own maps. Not using someone else's.
Yeah, but it's something to
remember where you started.
And one day, when you map the world,
you can look back on this one
and see how much better yours is.
You know what? You're right.
It's nice to remember
where we've come from.
You should do something for yourself too.
Something to help you remember
home before we leave it behind.
I didn't really have much growing up.
I don't think there's
something to remember.
Well, maybe not something.
But someone.
Uh…
Ah.
[chuckles]
[snail groans]
[curious music playing]
[woman grunts]
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
- [Zoro] Sorry about that.
- Ah. No, it's my fault.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
-Kuina. -[sighs]
What was that?
Nothing.
You just look like someone I used to know.
Well, thank you for your help.
Uh, maybe I could help you
in return? You seem lost.
I'm not lost!
I have a great sense of direction.
Okay.
There.
I'm going there.
Huh.
Was that…
Oh, come on.
Oh, that's it.
-[door opens] -[gasps, clears throat]
-[door closes] -Welcome, my young friend.
Uh, how can I serve you on this fine day?
I need new swords.
Of course you do. Well,
you've come to the right shop.
We've got old swords, new swords. The
finest blades in all of the East Blue.
Anything sharp your heart
desires can be purchased right here.
What'll this get me?
Bargain bin's over there.
Friend! Wait.
That sword on your belt, may…
May I see it?
Hmm.
Ah!
No, it's nothing impressive. My mistake.
Sorry.
But…
It's not in terrible condition,
and perhaps I can help you
with your lack of funding.
Say I give you 200,000 berry for it?
[Zoro] It's not for sale.
400,000.
And, uh…
and I'll let you pick any
three swords in the store.
-Is this haggling? -750,000, final offer.
Get one top-shelf sword and anything
else you can carry out in the entire store.
[woman] I knew I recognized it!
The Wado Ichimonji.
One of the 21 Great Grade blades.
[sighs, chuckles]
- You really know your swords.
- Kind of my thing.
I never imagined that I'd get
to see one like this in person.
To the right collector, this
would be worth tens of millions.
[grunts]
Hello, Matsu. [chuckles]
Tashigi, my favorite customer.
[Tashigi] I'm here to pick up Shigure.
Right, your sword. I'll go
get it. 300 berry, please.
It was only 200 last week.
Inflation's a bitch, ain't it?
[gasps]
Ipponmatsu offers the
best sword-sharpening care
if you're ever in need.
I bring Shigure in every week.
Best to leave such important
maintenance to a professional.
Uh…
Hey, since you know so much about swords,
wanna help me pick some?
Absolutely! [chuckles]
Hmm, let's see.
No, you don't want anything in here.
These are duller than feathers, or
they'll shatter before you can swing 'em.
You know, the best swords are more
than just creations for combat, though.
They're pieces of art.
History.
Each one has a story. A
personality. A purpose.
And a price tag.
What is that doing here?
What is it?
That's the Sandai Kitetsu.
- Cool name.
- You… you don't want that sword.
It's cursed.
The Sandai Kitetsu is third in a lineage
of magnificent but ill-fated swords.
Even renowned swordsmen who wield a
Kitetsu blade all meet a tragic end.
[Ipponmatsu] Crazy sword girl is right.
Most swordsmen wouldn't
dare use a Kitetsu these days.
I've been wanting to get
rid of that one for years,
but I'm afraid I'll get cursed too.
I am sorry, son, but I
cannot sell that to you.
How about we test what's stronger.
My will,
or the sword's curse?
If I win,
sell it to me.
What are you going to…
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ipponmatsu grunts]
I'll take it.
[Tashigi scoffs]
And one more.
Wait.
[Tashigi gasps]
Wait right there.
[Luffy] Oh, Sanji! I can't believe
there's so much food from the East Blue
that I've never tried before.
I just want to eat it all.
Yeah, no, I get it. It's nice to taste
the flavors from home before we leave,
but think of all the new things we're
gonna try when we get into the Grand Line.
I can't stop thinking about it.
What?
What is this thing?
- That is a blue-finned elephant tuna.
- Yeah.
They're actually native to the South Blue.
[chuckles] Good eye! You
really know your stuff.
Well, you know, I've experimented a bit.
He's the best cook in the whole East Blue.
[chuckles] Well, if you want it,
it's yours. It's the last one anyway.
The restaurant Baratie took
almost everything I have.
Adding a new item to their menu.
True blue-fin sauté. [chuckles]
That sounds like the dish you made.
That is the dish I made.
So the old geezer stole
it and put it on the menu.
Sounds like Zeff liked it.
I guess he did.
Well, then, I'm gonna have to keep
impressing him. So I'll take this beauty.
And what else you got?
[chuckles] Follow me.
[Sanji] Luffy, stay here.
[Usopp] And then the whole
tower came crashing down.
[mimics crashing noises]
Then the village threw a party
in my honor for saving them.
I haven't been gone long, but it's
already some of my craziest adventures yet.
By the time you get this message,
we'll be in the Grand Line.
And… I can't help but be a little…
nervous.
But my crew needs me! [sighs]
And what kind of captain
would let his people down?
Yeah, honestly, I don't know
what they'd do without me, Kaya.
I'm sure she misses you too, Usopp.
Out of the way, lady.
You lose something?
[scoffs]
[Nami giggles]
Give me back my wallet, you thief.
I'd call you one too, but
I don't think it applies.
You don't know what you're talking
about. I run things here in Loguetown.
That's why the streets are so safe.
Can I offer you some friendly advice?
No.
Maybe.
Pick a better mark.
Look for some idiot
who's distracted or lost.
Isolate them.
Lure them in with the
promise of something they want.
Then, when their guard is down,
you take what you want.
Whatever.
I don't need advice from you.
[chuckles]
Happy hunting!
-Who was that? -Just some rookie.
[wind whistling]
Huh.
[Usopp] What's wrong?
Air pressure changed.
A storm is coming.
What do you mean? I don't feel any rain.
A storm is not just about rain.
There's static in the air.
We need to find the others.
And then get the hell out of here.
That's Yubashiri.
My store may not be much, but, um…
this is the best sword I have.
It's a family heirloom.
Black lacquer tachi sword with
a small clove wild-pattern blade.
One of only 50 Skillful
Grade swords in the world.
I told you I don't have much money.
I'm not asking for money.
Just take it.
And forgive me
for, uh, trying to trick you earlier.
It's, uh…
It's been too long…
since I looked in the
eyes of a worthy swordsman.
And as they say,
a sword
chooses its owner.
And I will pray for your
continued good fortune.
And, uh, thanks for your help.
Hope to meet again someday.
I hope so too.
[man] Hey, look. Look.
[Luffy] Uh, excuse me. I'm
looking for the execution platform.
[overlapping chatter]
Do you guys know where
the execution platform is?
[man 2] Get lost.
Okay.
[singing in Italian]
[coin clatters]
Wow.
[yelling] Do you know where
the execution platform is?
[man continues singing]
[yelling] It's… it's okay.
I'll come back when you finish your song.
[grunts]
Hello, mark.
I mean, mate. [chuckles]
Huh?
You wouldn't happen to be looking for
Gold Roger's execution platform, would ya?
That is exactly what I'm looking for.
Isn't this your lucky day? I
was just heading in that direction.
Name's Bartolomeo.
And I'm famous around this city for my
hospitality.
Wow.
What's it like being famous?
Oh, I'll tell you all about it. [chuckles]
[Luffy] Wow.
-[circus music playing] -[thunder rumbling]
[Bartolomeo] Hmm.
[Luffy] Look! That's it.
The King of the Pirates died over there.
[Bartolomeo] Never gave
two shits about the guy.
Marines just make a big deal every
year, trying to remind us of the rules.
Get caught, get dead. [chuckles]
[Luffy] This is where
the Great Pirate Era began.
[Bartolomeo] That why you want
to see this place so bad, huh?
[Luffy] Wow.
Everything I've done,
everywhere I go,
it all started here.
I just wanted to see it for myself.
[chuckles]
[unsettling circus music playing]
Don't you have a dream you want to follow?
Uh…
I never thought about that.
Hey!
[grunts]
Huh?
[suspenseful music playing]
You miss me, dickbag?
Who the hell are you?
Bunny.
It's Buggy!
[woman] Hey, that's Buggy.
You know my name, you
stretchy little shitlick.
- I said that.
- It's Bug… It's Buggy the Clown.
That's not what you said. Oh
God, I forgot how annoying you are.
And who is this?
Let me guess. New crew member?
You must be the ship's
stylist?
I wanna make fun of you, but,
honestly, I love what you're doing.
- Sure you wouldn't be better off with us?
- He's famous around here, you know?
His name is...
[laughs]
I'm nobody.
I got nothing to do with him
or you or any other pirate.
-I'm outta here. [chuckles] -Hey,
come on. What's the rush, friend?
You know, I love a bit
of audience participation.
[Luffy] What do you want anyway?
How'd you find me this time?
[music swells]
I knew you'd come here.
Drawn like a shit moth to a shit flame.
But that doesn't ever work out
well for the moth, now, does it?
Oh, I can see it now!
Old Shanksy bouncing you on his knee,
filling your head up with all the
stories of Gold Roger's final curtain call,
dreaming
that one day, you'd come
to stand in his shadow.
Is this another one of your shows?
Oh, no. Tonight's not a show.
Tonight
is a lesson.
And it's where your brief, pathetic
little journey comes to an end.
It's a shame your friends
aren't here to see it.
[yelling] But lucky for you,
I brought some friends of my own.
Oh, honey bunny!
I am not your honey bunny, clown.
[onlookers murmuring]
Alvida?
Her name you remember?
You met her once.
I've been thinking about this
for a long time, Straw Hat.
Yeah, it's… it's been a while.
How's your ship?
You lit it on fire.
[exhales] Right. Whoa.
Whoo.
Anyways, gotta get going,
guys. Grand Line's calling.
Oh, you're not walking
out of here alive. [laughs]
So you want a fight?
Take your best shot.
Okay.
Gum Gum…
Pistol!
[onlookers laughing]
[chuckles]
How did you do that?
Who the hell are you guys?
She's a real knockout,
huh? I'm pretty lucky.
[Alvida chuckles] Same
trick won't work twice.
Not anymore.
I ate the Slip Slip Fruit.
Whatever you throw at me slides right off.
I don't care about your devil fruit.
You still can't beat me.
[Alvida] Oh, we'll see about that.
I am Captain Iron Mace Alvida,
the most powerful and ruthless
pirate in the East Blue,
and I will have my vengeance.
Slip Slip Tracks!
Huh?
[onlookers cheering]
[grunts]
[Luffy] Aah!
-[onlookers cheer] -That's our cue!
[man] Take the cuffs up.
[Buggy] All right, make
some room, you idiots.
[man] You ain't going anywhere!
I feel
funny.
[echoing] So woozy.
That's 'cause those new bracelets
of yours are made of seastone.
You ever heard of it?
It's an element with all the
properties of the sea itself.
It saps you of all your
obnoxiously spirited stamina.
And the best part is, it nullifies
your little devil fruit powers.
Just like seawater.
So there's no running
away, and no fighting back.
-Stay with us, pal. -[Luffy snoring].
You don't wanna miss what comes next.
[laughs]
[all laughing]
[marching military music playing]
Captain Smoker! Sir, pirates have
been sighted at the execution platform.
Surround the area.
- No one moves till I arrive.
- [Marines] Yes, sir.
-Oh! -[man gasps]
Sir, we're so sorry.
Apologize to the captain.
Uh…
Looks like my pants ate your ice cream.
Buy more scoops this time.
Gee, thanks, mister!
[man] Let's go home. Come.
What? Are you waiting for ice cream too?
-Go! -Yes, Captain Smoker!
[Tashigi] Captain!
You're late, petty officer.
-Sorry, sir, I was just... -I don't care.
You messed up the buttons on your jacket.
Where are we going?
To do our job.
- [man] They're over there.
- [woman] Might as well.
Where are they?
Zoro!
[Zoro] Ah.
Oh, you got the swords.
Here's your money.
I didn't need it.
- You didn't kill anyone for those?
- [Zoro] No.
I haggled.
Okay.
Well, you still owe me interest.
Those look like really nice swords.
And someone just gave them to you?
Yeah, pretty much.
Suspicious.
Okay, look, there's a storm coming.
A big one. We need to
get back to the Merry.
- Sanji! You get everything you needed?
- [Sanji] Yes.
I had everything sent to
the Merry. Except this beauty.
She is not leaving my sight.
[Zoro] Where's Luffy?
I thought he would have come back already.
You lost him?
[Zoro] He remembers the
fish, but loses our captain.
Look, we know where he has to be.
If anything happens to him, you'll
be the first I use my new sword...
Stop! Stop! Stop!
We need to find him.
Uh, guys, where's everybody going?
[man] Excuse me.
[man 2] Pirates at the execution platform.
- [woman] They have devil fruit powers.
- [Nami] Luffy!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Alvida] My fellow pirates,
citizens of Loguetown,
the charges against this buffoon
known as Monkey D. Luffy are as follows.
He destroyed my ship,
kidnapped my precious Koby,
and turned him against me,
and worst of all, daring to call
himself the future King of the Pirates.
[laughter]
The only justified sentence… [chuckles]
…is death.
[onlookers] Yeah!
[muffled speech]
Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh!
Sh, sh, sh, sh!
As your lawyer,
I advise that you let me do the talking.
[clicks tongue]
Friends,
good freaks, and residents of Loguetown,
lend me your ears.
Now, is Luffy a stupid little dipshit?
[jeering]
Yeah.
And should we all be deeply humiliated
that he has somehow become the
most wanted pirate in the East Blue?
Of course.
[onlookers] Yeah!
And is he so insufferably obnoxious
that sometimes you just want to
rip that ridiculous hat off his head
and cram it down his throat?
-[laughter] -Absolutely.
I know I do.
[onlookers murmur]
[Buggy] But even with all that,
does he really deserve to die?
[onlookers murmuring]
The answer is yes, and I rest my case!
[cheering]
[Buggy] Well, the system works.
[Luffy grunts]
You are not a very good lawyer.
Don't you understand the lesson yet, kid?
The most powerful thing
in the world isn't a weapon
or a devil fruit or even a dream.
It's a story.
[Alvida] But all stories end.
Including yours.
Today!
[onlookers] Yeah!
[Buggy] And all of these fine folks
are gonna bear witness.
The boy who would be king
chopped down
before he ever left the East Blue.
[Sanji] Luffy?
Sanji!
Oh, good. The Shit Hats made it.
Take care of the Luff troupe
while I move on with the main event?
[Alvida] Ugh! Out of my way!
[overlapping chatter]
So you want to be like the
King of the Pirates, huh?
Well, be careful what you wish for.
[Luffy grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
Get 'em.
[crowd clamors]
[grunts]
Huh?
[grunting]
[Cabaji] At last,
our rematch, Roronoa Zoro.
I don't have time for this.
[grunts]
[men grunt]
[Cabaji yells]
Hmm.
Nice.
[action music playing]
[grunting]
[Alvida laughs]
How are you doing that?
I'm slippery from head to toe.
Know when you're beat, little girl.
-[yells] -Nami!
Special attack! Pepper star.
[gasps]
[sneezes]
[screaming]
Was that my pepper?
Another round in Captain
Usopp's mighty arsenal.
-[man] There he is! Get him! -[gasps]
[clamoring]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
Should we go in?
No.
Let the pirates tear each other apart.
When they're done, we'll clean
up whoever's left standing.
He's a pirate.
I'll show you the last
thing Gold Roger ever saw,
besides his guts spilling out!
Yeah!
Any last words, Captain Shit-tacular?
My name is Monkey D. Luffy!
[grunting]
[Luffy] I will find the One Piece
and become King of the Pirates!
[man 2] Let's get him.
[grunting]
Loud!
You don't know
the first thing about being a king.
I know you'll never be one.
[laughs]
[grunting]
Well, heavy is the head
that wears the crown.
So let's take yours off.
Shall we?
[grunting]
Ha!
[yelps]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Luffy] Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp!
Nami!
I'm sorry.
I'm dead.
That smile.
Luffy!
[clamoring]
[laughing]
[grunting]
That laugh.
Roger.
[grunting]
[laughs] I'm dead!
[grunts]
[screams]
Not again!
-[Zoro gasps] -[gasps]
[Luffy grunts]
[grunts]
[sighs, blubbers]
[uplifting music playing]
[sighs]
Lucky me.
All right.
Everyone okay?
[Usopp] Us?
You just got struck by lightning.
Luffy, we need to get back to the ship.
[Captain Smoker] Hold it!
You're all under arrest by
the authority of the Marines.
There's an exit that way.
Get the hell out of here!
Thanks.
My bags!
Do not let those pirates leave this city!
- Sanji would kill me if I left this!
- Wait! Where are Nami and Usopp?
-Did they get lost? -Nami doesn't get lost.
-Probably at the Merry. -This way!
- [Tashigi] Stop right there.
- [Luffy gasps] Huh?
Or not. [sighs]
Angry ex?
Get to the ship. I got this.
[Sanji] Hmm.
[Tashigi] Should've put it together sooner.
You're Roronoa Zoro.
Bounty hunter turned pirate.
- Then you know you don't wanna do this.
- [Tashigi] Oh, I do.
I'm going to take the
Wado Ichimonji from you.
[sighs] Let's see you try.
[suspenseful action music playing]
[Tashigi grunting]
You didn't tell me you were a Marine.
You didn't ask.
So the sword geek can fight too.
Better than you. Dropping your elbow.
[panting]
You're a brute.
No matter how hard you fight,
there will always be someone
better than you with a blade.
I won't surrender this sword for anything.
Especially not you.
Why won't you kill me?
You're no great swordsman.
You're not worthy of the Wado
Ichimonji or any other blade!
[Luffy laughing]
[Captain Smoker] Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm Captain Smoker of the Marines.
You're not going anywhere.
Yeah, sorry, Smokey, but we're
kind of in a hurry right now.
I got this.
[yells]
[grunts]
He has a devil fruit!
Doesn't matter. We take him out.
-[grunts] -[yells]
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting]
Gum Gum…
Gatling!
[exhales]
Sanji!
[scoffs] Small fries.
White Blow!
[Luffy grunts]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[Luffy] Aah! Aah! Aah!
[grunting]
You're worth 30 million berry.
Aah! [grunts]
[coughing]
[Captain Smoker] Looks
like your luck's run out.
[Luffy coughing]
[Captain Smoker chuckles]
Whose luck did you say?
You.
Who are we to stand in the
way of another man's voyage?
World Government wants your head.
Hmm. Not today.
The world is still waiting for our answer.
[Captain Smoker grunts]
[mysterious music playing]
-[coughing] -[Sanji] Luffy?
Let's go.
Hey. Come on.
Come on.
The hell happened back there?
I'm not sure.
Rain's about to hit.
Zoro, Usopp, drop the sails!
That guy who saved you, who was that?
No idea.
[thunder crashes]
[mysterious man] Huh, a pirate, hey?
That's fine if that's what you have chosen.
Go forth.
Not exactly what you signed up for,
is it, little bird?
Who are you?
Someone who also understands what
it feels like to be kept in a cage.
I gather you're more used to paper
cuts than these kinds of wounds.
Even still,
they must hurt less than your pride.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I know you have potential
that is being squandered.
I know you have skills that are wasted.
Desires that aren't being met.
I know you're strong.
Intelligent.
Beautiful.
This world has so much more
to offer you, little bird.
And you can have all of it.
What's this?
[woman] Wings.
[Captain Smoker] Tashigi.
Captain Smoker.
What are you doing here?
[Captain Smoker] Thanks, Raoul.
Mmm.
Gold Roger used to frequent this bar.
They say he even had his final drink
here before he set out into the Grand Line.
After he was captured and killed,
the place kind of lost its draw.
Kill the man,
kill the legend.
So we thought.
[thunder rumbles]
I come here every anniversary of his death
to remind myself what I'm fighting for.
What I'm fighting against.
And what is that, sir?
I was there, you know.
The day Gold Roger was executed.
You know what he did when he faced his end?
He laughed.
[unsettling music playing]
I was just a boy,
but even I could see
the effect his words had.
The promise of the One Piece
drove the world into chaos.
No child should have to live
through that kind of madness.
And that's what I'm fighting for.
Dedicated my life to making sure the
world never sees another Gold Roger.
Ah.
Rest up. Tomorrow, we head out.
Head out? To…
-To where? -The clown spilled the beans.
The Straw Hats are
heading for the Grand Line.
We're gonna hunt 'em down.
He laughed, Tashigi.
Straw Hat Luffy looked death
in the face, and he laughed.
That's what we're fighting against.
[adventurous music playing]
Guys! Look!
[Nami] We made it!
[Usopp] Is that…
Reverse Mountain.
The entrance to the Grand Line.
Our journey gets a lot harder from here.
Harder than Warlords?
Killer sharks?
Whoever that lady with the mace was?
Yeah.
But there's nothing we can't take on
together!
Grand Line,
here we come!
Whoo!
[laughs] Yahoo!
Yeah!
[adventurous music continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[man singing in Italian]